hostadvice.com 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Host Advice

## What information do we collect?

You may choose to visit our site anonymously; however, when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form, we collect pertinent information. You may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information depending on how you are using the site.

As a third party vendor Google uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## What do we use your information for?

We may use any of the information we collect from in order to:

  * Personalize your experience
  * Respond better to your individual needs
  * Improve our website based on user information and feedback
  * Improve customer service
  * Process transactions
  * Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * Send periodic emails

## How do we protect your information?

The information we obtain from you will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
We may use your provided email address to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, occasional company news or updates, and related product or service information. However, you have the choice to opt out of receiving future emails by following the detailed unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each email.

We implement a wide array of security measures to ensure and maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential.

We do not store any personal financial information on our servers after a transaction.

## Do we use cookies?

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we release any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  
This excludes trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
When we believe release is appropriate in order to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves and others, we may also release your information .

## Third party links

At our discretion, we may include or offer occasional third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies; therefore, we do not assume any responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Because we seek to protect the integrity of our site,, we do welcome any feedback about these other sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We agree to not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the site and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all aimed at those who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our [contact us](http://hosttracer.com/contact-us/) page.
